ntere.st 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | i.ntere.st

i.ntere.st will handle all user information in connection with the i.ntere.st’s service (the “Service”) as follows;

## 1\. Acquisition of Personal Information

i.ntere.st will only acquire personal information by legitimate means.

## 2\. Purpose of Use of Personal Information

i.ntere.st will use the personal information which i.ntere.st acquires for the following purposes. Except where permitted under the Law Concerning Protection of Personal Information ("Personal Information Protection Law") or any other relevant law or regulation, i.ntere.st will not use an individual's personal information for any purpose outside of those listed below, without that individual's prior consent.

  1. to offer an undisturbed and smooth the Service to users
  2. to aggregate statistical data regarding the Service
  3. to conduct research and analysis aimed at reviewing and improving the Services
  4. to provide information regarding the Service as well as advertising information
  5. to improve the Service and the systems
  6. to deliver gifts
  7. to perform identity checks when a user makes an inquiry etc.
  8. to prevent any unauthorized/fraudulent use of the Service
  9. to notify users of any other important information regarding the Service and to contact users where necessary

## 3\. Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties

i.ntere.st will comply with the Personal Information Protection Law and all other relevant laws and regulations regarding the provision of personal information to third parties.

  * Shared Use of Information

i.ntere.st may share your personal information with a business partner, when a business partner's cooperation is needed in order to keep providing the Service to the user. In such circumstances, i.ntere.st will inform you of the purpose of information sharing, the name of the business partner and information manager, as well as the type of shared information involved before sharing your personal information with such a business partner.

## 4\. Requests Regarding Personal Information

If i.ntere.st receives a request from an individual whose personal information i.ntere.st holds to disclose, amend, supplement or delete that information, or to temporarily suspend or permanently cease the use of that information, to cease providing that information to a third party, or to inform that individual of the purpose of use of that information, i.ntere.st will promptly respond to that request in good faith in accordance with the Personal Information Protection Law, after first confirming that the request is from the individual to whom the information relates.  
Please note that i.ntere.st may not be able to respond to your request if it does not meet the requirements of the Personal Information Protection Law, or if i.ntere.st is authorized by that law or other related legislations to refuse your request for disclosure or otherwise.

## 5\. Cookies

To provide the best possible service to user, as well as for maintenance and security purposes, Cookies will be used to store user’s settings, to record access figures as well as monitoring usage patterns and statistics. You can choose to deactivate Cookies, however in such circumstances you will not be able to use parts of the Service which require Cookies to be active such as those requiring you to login.

## 6\. Remove Information

You can close your i.ntere.st account at any time. When you close your account, i.ntere.st will deactivate it and remove all information connected to your i.ntere.st account from the Service. Such information cannot be backed-up or restored.

## 7\. Contact for Inquiries

All requests, opinions, questions, complaints and other inquiries with respect to i.ntere.st’s handling of personal information should be referred to the following address.

## 8\. Continuous Improvement

i.ntere.st continuously strives to improve our policies and procedures for the handling of personal information, and as a result this privacy policy may be amended, as required.

Day of Enactment: March 20, 2011

Date of Revision: February 24, 2012

Date of Last Revision: July 31, 2014

以上
